{"data":[{"question":"Because ________ food is as nutritious for a baby as its mother's milk, many women are returning to the practice of breast feeding.","a":"not","b":"no","c":"none","d":"some","answer":"2","explain":"\n- No: used as a determiner followed by a noun (not any)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Civil engineers had better ________ to use steel supports in concrete structures built on unstable geophysical sites.","a":"planning","b":"to plan","c":"plan","d":"plans","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Had better do sth = should do something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Three dangerous criminals escaped ________ prison yesterday.","a":"from","b":"for","c":"out","d":"for","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Escape from.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The exam results could ________ your career.","a":"determinant","b":"determination","c":"determine","d":"determined","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Modal verb (can\/may\/ must\/ will...)+ infinitive (without To).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"If the oxygen supply in the atmosphere ________ replenished by plants, it would soon be exhausted.","a":"were not","b":"was not","c":"had not been","d":"has not been","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Conditional sentence type 2: If + past simple, S + would\/should + V.\u00a0\n- In condition type 2: to be - were.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"I used to earn ________ money, but then I lost my job.","a":"a lot of","b":"many","c":"lot","d":"few","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A lot of + uncountable\/countable noun.\u00a0\n- Many\/few+ countable noun.\u00a0\n- Lot never stands alone, we say: a lot\/lot of...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The practical and legal implications of euthanasia, the practice of causing the death of a person suffering from an incurable disease, are so controversial ________ it is illegal in most countries.","a":"as","b":"when","c":"since","d":"that","answer":"4","explain":"\n- So\/such...that: used when emphasizing the degree or amount of something by saying what the result is.\u00a0\n+ So + adj + that.\u00a0\n+ Such + noun phrase- Such + Noun phrase (adj + noun).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Since lightning was probably significant in the formation of life, understanding it might help us ________ life itself.","a":"understanding","b":"understand","c":"understood","d":"to understanding","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Help somebody do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Starfishes and sea urchins, members of the echinoderms or spiny skinned animals, are particularly ________ because of their unusual structures.","a":"to interest","b":"interest","c":"interested","d":"interesting","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Adverb can be used to modify adjective, normal verb but never modify noun.\u00a0\n- Something is interesting to sbd; somebody feels interested in sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"________ poetry is more enjoyable when it is read aloud.","a":"Almost","b":"Most","c":"Many","d":"Few","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Many\/few + countable noun.\u00a0\n- Almost: is adverb (modifies verb or adj).\u00a0\n- Most: can be determiner\/pronoun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"}]}